Ah!
Mister.
What are you doing?
Isn't this what you asked for?
What,
forgot?
I...
Close your eyes.
Wait.
Mister,
do you
really like me?
Girl...
I...
The Demonic Cult!
The Demonic Cult is invading!
Seeking death.
Attack!
Protect A-Kong!
Mister,
you haven't recovered yet.
Let me go.
Commander Ye,
stay and protect him.
Okay.
But you have to use this.
It seems Longyuan likes its new master.
Go.
Who is that?
So powerful.
It's Madam.
What a powerful sword.
It can actually merge
with my spiritual power.
Little one,
not bad.
Bai Ze,
why are you here?
To protect you, of course.
How affectionate.
But I advise Mr. Bai to marry her quickly,
before she climbs into someone else's bed
and you regret it.
With the enemy right in front of us,
Miss Feng still has the mood to joke.
Little one, wait for me.
I'll help you.
Longyuan only recognizes one master.
It chooses for itself.
Even Longyuan recognizes her.
Then what am I?
I've waited a thousand years,
and even a sword understands him
better than I do.
I will take good care of Qingwu.
You said you would take care of me.
Is this how you take care of me?
Now you only have eyes
for that girl of unknown origin.
Bai Ze!
You...
Woman,
can't you even tell friend from foe?
If that's the case,
don't stay on the battlefield
and cause trouble.
How are you?
Are you badly hurt?
Little one.
I'm fine.
Girl,
are you hurt?
Mister, I'm fine.
That's good.
The enemies are mostly dealt with.
Come back with me.
But
what just happened...
Sect Leader Yan saw it all, right?
If you can't even manage
your own subordinates,
then don't take her away.
Ah!
Mr. Bai, I will never forget
you saving my life today.
As for the girl...
Ah!
what happens between us
has nothing to do with Mr. Bai.